NAFISA MOHAMED

&: 079 6154 1152

157 Hamstead Road Birmingham B20 2RH

SKILLS

I Analytical I
I Problem Solving I
I Strong Business Acumen I
I Organized I
I Dedicated I
I Team Worker I
I Excellent Interpersonal Skills
I Communication I
I Debt Resolution I
I Complaint Handling I
I High Standard
Customer Service I
I Perseverance I
I Proficient in Excel I
I Multilingual I

Profile

A pro-active, confident and articulate processing administrator and finance associate with over 4 years 'experience in the finance industry. Assisted in an optimized utilization strategy for various service providers and technology advances resulting in real, tangible differences to the success of the business. Worked with high-level decision-making groups, analyzing business processes and systems. Demonstrated excellent team working, communication and organization skills together with strong commitment, enthusiasm and drive. My goal is to develop a career in a leading and progressive establishment.

Experience

Business Support Officer, Birmingham & Solihull Women's Aid - 2022-2022 Undertaking research and information gathering activities and providing management information data as requested. Servicing meetings as required, including planning and preparation, providing general support, taking and distributing minutes and typing up flip charts and notes. Developing and maintaining an effective progress chasing system. Setting up and maintaining appropriate, effective and efficient office systems as required. Leading ad hoc projects as directed by the EA

Finance Associate, Johnson Controls — 2017 - 2022

Using Various ERP systems (Mentor/JDE/SUN/SAP/Sage) as well as Business Support Tools; E-invoicing and CRM tools. Pro requests received from the field for order processing, invoicing and reviewing potential business liability issues from data inaccuracies across relevant operational areas. Interact with the Customer Account and Operational Teams to identify improvements to processes and assist in customer dispute resolution to create solutions to upstream failures.

Processing Administrator, Johnson Controls — 2015 - 2017

Provide customer satisfaction through the participation in an efficient and responsive processing environment. Resolve problems by clarifying issues; researching and exploring answers, implementing solutions and escalating unresolved problems. Updating customer records efficiently in keeping with data protection

Case Administrator, Department for Work and Pensions — 2014 - 2015 Effectively and proactively manage all internal queries, concerns or requests for appeals. Provide Administration services to the Department and wider teams within DWP with accurate data collation and analysis for reporting purposes. Maintain information storage and retrieval systems.

Education

University of Wolverhampton — BSc Biomedical Science 2014

References Available upon Request